visacommunities.com 2017-07-05

# 

  * **YOUR PRIVACY AT VISACOMMUNITIES NETWORK**

When registering you do not need to provide any information except the bare minimum that we need for your account: a username, email and a password. Unlike many other sites we will never share your email and password with third parties in any manner unless required/demanded by lawful authority . We collect no personal information about you when you visit our website. If you have any suggestions on how we can improve, please don't hesitate to contact us.

  * **WHAT WE COLLECT AND STORE AUTOMATICALLY**

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. Rather, Information is kept in the aggregate. We automatically collect and store only the information about your visit. we use the information we collect to understand the traffic to our site (for example it is important to know how much bandwidth the site uses so that we can purchase more if needed, if the "hits" to our site increase we need to pay more money for better hosting), and to help us to make our site more useful to visitors like you.

  * **IF YOU SEND US EMAIL:**

You may choose to provide us with personal information, as in email with a comment or question. We use the information to improve our services to you or to respond to your requests. Except for authorized law enforcement Investigations/enquiries, we do not share our email with any other outside organizations.

  * **COOKIES** : 
  * **A)** VISITING THE SITE – if all you do is visit and surf the site, no cookies are used.
  * **B)** LOGGING IN - if you decide to use a cookie (this is done by checking the box that logs you in automatically) to save you logging in every time you visit Visacommunities Network. Cookies help us create a speedy web experience by remembering your user name and email information, so you don't have to re type it when signing in. Cookies do not store personal information and we do not use them to track your movements through our site and you do not need cookies to use this site (you will simply have to log in at every visit) it's your choice.
  * **c)** SPELL CHECK -The spell check has the ability to learn from you. That means that if a word is consistently marked as a misspelled word (a member's name that is not in the dictionary for example )you can click the button "learn" in the spell checker and this word will be saved to a cookie so that it will not be marked as a misspelled word in the future. If you do not use this feature the spell checker does not use any cookies. If at any time we add anything else that uses a cookie the privacy policy will be updated. If you find a cookie from our site that you think does not fall under one of those categories please contact us.
  * **D)** Google as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve advertisements on our site.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to other sites on the internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

  * **POSTING TO THE SITE:**

If you post a message on the site it is stored in a database. The pages then display information from the database so that others can read your post on the forums. This is how any dynamic site works, the text has to be stored somewhere so that it can be displayed.

  * **LINKS TO OTHER SITES:**

Our website has links to partners and other sites. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.

  * **RESTRICTION OF LIABILITY:**

Visacommunities network makes no claims, promises or guarantees about the accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this website and expressly disclaims liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this website.

No warranty of any kind, implied, expressed or statutory, including but not limited to the warranties of non-infringement of third party rights, title, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose and freedom from computer virus, is given with respect to the contents of this website or its hyperlinks to other Internet resources.

Reference in this website to any specific commercial products, processes or services, or the use of any trade, firm or corporation name is for the information and convenience of the public only, and does not constitute endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by Visacommunities network in any manner.

Advertisements are subject to the privacy policy of those concerned advertising sites. Visacommunities network has no liability for such use/misuse of such sites and any information collected on Visacommunities Network websites is not shared except to comply with Law if required.
